Hello?
مرحبا؟
He's not there. Who's speaking?
انه ليس هنا. من الذي يتحدث؟
Sorry, the Prince of where?
آسف، أمير ماذا؟
Which one?
أي واحد؟
No, no. No, which prince? Not which Wales.
لا، لا. لا، أي أمير؟ ليس أى ويلز.
-What year is this? -I think that's probably for me!
- وماذا هو هذا العام؟ - أعتقد أن هذا ربما لي!
Hold this.
امسك هذا
Hello? Ah, yes, everything's fine. Don't worry.
مرحبا؟ آه، نعم، كل شيء على ما يرام. لا تقلق.
Well, exactly. Why should you be worrying?
حسنا، بالضبط. لماذا يجب أن تكون قلق؟
Who even mentioned worrying?
من الذي ذكر حتى القلق؟
She's fine. No, your mum is fine.
هى على ما يرام. لا، أمك على ما يرام.
Don't answer this phone. I answer this phone.
لا تجيبى على هذا الهاتف. أنا أجيب على هذا الهاتف.
-Where have you been? -Party. Just a party.
- وأنت أين كنت؟ - ودى, فقط حفلة
Um, yes, your mum is here, actually,
نعم، أمك هنا، في الواقع
but she can't come to the phone at the moment.
لكنها لا يمكن أن تأتي إلى الهاتف في هذه اللحظة.
Well, she's busy.
حسنا، انها مشغولة.
Oh, you know, the Commonwealth.
انت تعرف، الرابطة الشعبية.
It's your son, ma'am, he wants to talk to you.
انه ابنك، يا سيدتي، انه يريد التحدث معك.
We can't let him see you like this,
لا يمكننا السماح له رؤيتك مثل هذا،
well, hear you, not that he could hear you,
حسنا، يسمعك، ليس انه يمكن ان يسمعك،
-you're a fish. -(PHONE RINGS)
انت سمكة
Sorry, I've got another call coming in.
آسف، لدى مكالمة أخرى قادمة.
Hello?
مرحبا؟
There is not a bit of use yelling, ambassador.
ليس هناك فائدة من استخدام الصراخ، يا سفير.
Your warrior chief is trapped in my Tardis.
رئيس محاربيك محاصر فى التارديس
And until you've turned Her Majesty here back into a human being,
وحتى تحول صاحبة الجلالة هنا مرة أخرى إلى إنسانة،
he's staying put. Don't worry, he's perfectly safe...
انه باق. لا تقلق، انه آمن تماما ...
Just popping you on hold.
فقط ساضعك على الانتظار.
What have you done?
ماذا فعلت؟
I thought that it was a fly.
اعتقدت أنه كان الطائر.
So much for the slaughter of 10 billion souls.
كثير على ذبح 10 مليار نسمة.
-What is going on? -I was at a party.
- ماذا يجري؟ - كنت فى حفلة
There was a slight incident.
كان هناك حادث بسيط.
What, so you sneak out at night to parties?
ماذا، اذن انت تتسلل فى الليل الى الحفلات؟
Hang on. You're dressed up. You never dress up.
لحظة. انت متأنق. انت لا تتأنق ابدا
-Was River at the party? -Oh, why would she be there?
- هل كانت ريفر فى الحفلة؟ - لماذا تكون هناك؟
Don't... Just don't lie to me, Doctor.
لا ... فقط لا تكذب علي، يا دكتور.
-You're rubbish at it. -Look, I do not sneak out at night
- انت سخيف فى ذلك - انظرى, أنا لا التسلل ليلا
-See? Rubbish. -Oh!
ارأيت؟ هراء
Look, sorry, but I am in the middle of a thing.
انظرى، آسف، ولكن أنا في وسط شيء.
Doctor!
دكتور!
Doctor.
دكتور
I... I need to talk to you.
أنا ... أنا بحاجة إلى التحدث معك.
There is a reason that I couldn't sleep.
هناك سبب لانني لم أستطع النوم.
-Rory! -What are you doing?
- رورى - ماذا تفعل؟
You've got the serious face on.
لديك الوجه الخطير.
I always shout for Rory when you've got the serious face.
أنا دائما اصرخ لروري عندما يكون لديك الوجه الخطير.
Rory, she's having an emotion!
روري، انها لديها انفعال!
-What? What's wrong, Amy? -Why are you calling him?
- ماذا؟ ما هو الخطأ، ايمي؟ - لماذا تدعوه؟
It's his turn.
انه دوره.
You two have... You two have turns?
هل انتم ... أنتم بالتناوب؟
No!
لا!
It's the wrong fish. I've taken the wrong fish.
انها السمكة الخطأ. لقد اخذت السمكة الخطأ.
River, we've got the wrong fish.
ريفر، نحن قد اخذنا السمكة الخطأ.
Look, sorry, you two. I've made a mistake.
انظروا، آسف، انتم الاثنين. لقد ارتكبت خطأ.
I've got three hours to save the Commonwealth.
أنا عندي ثلاث ساعات لإنقاذ الرابطة الشعبية
What happens in three hours?
ماذا يحدث في ثلاث ساعات؟
The pet shops open.
متاجر الحيوانات الاليفة ستفتح.